ROHAN GUPTA

MARKETER

ABOUT ME

Strong in design and analytical skills. Skilled in developing business plans, customer segmentation, documentation and marketing campaigns. Strong written and verbal communications. Advanced knowledge of Python, Java and dart with specialized frameworks like Flask, flutter and Django. Cross platform web/app development.

SKILLS

Digital Marketing

Lead Generation

Motion Graphics

Pitching

Python

Java

Flask

Django

Flutter

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

• April 2016 - Present

Event Manager and Host

Hosted several formal and informal events for schools, organizations, businesses and private events.

• February 2015 - Present

MODEL UNITED NATIONS

Participated and won in 15+ MUNs across the country

COURSES AND CERTIFICATION

- Fundamentals of digital marketing By Google -Google Digital Garage
- The Complete Digital Marketing Course 12 Courses in 1 - Udemy

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 • Thapar Institute of Engineering and technology

2008 - 2020 • Kendriya Vidyalaya Kathmandu

EXPERIENCE

May 2021 - Present Project Manager, Enactus Thapar, Patiala

- Spreading awareness about issues related women through our Instagram and LinkedIn page.
- Installed sanitary pad vending machine in the campus
- Ready to launch a women safety app in the market
- Designed the workflow and the marketing strategies for the project, and prepared several sales pitches for the organization.

September 2021 - Present Co-founder, Karmaya, Kathmandu

- Building a community of enthusiastic youngsters with a motivation to do something good for the society.
- Organized fund-raisers for orphans
- Working on spreading awareness about our organization.

April 2018 - August 2018 Private Tutor

• Taught 4 students high school level mathematics and science.

ACHIVEMENTS

- Business case study competition, AIESEC in Patiala - Winner
- Makeathon, MLSC TIET Winner
- ACM Hacklipse Winner
- DSC WOW Top 10 Finalists
- Adobe Analytics Challenge Results awaited